https://www.phigam.org/2016/admin/privacy-policy-2016

Search
AboutThe Greater FraternityAwardsHistoryThe Archives of Phi Gamma DeltaToday in Phi Gam HistoryDigital RepositoryInternational LeadershipArchonsArchon BiosAppointed General OfficersSection ChiefsPurple LegionnairesMission, Vision & ValuesMembershipOur ChaptersUndergraduate Chapter DirectoryGraduate Chapter DirectoryShop FijiInternational HeadquartersIHQMuseum & LibraryStaff DirectoryStaff OpeningsCoordinator of CommunicationsField Secretary ProgramContact UsPhi Gamma Delta's Strategic PlanPositive Impact 2030Strategic PrioritiesAnnual ReportBuilding Courageous LeadersThe Leadership InstituteSubmit Story of Courageous LeadershipExpansionOverview & TimelineExpansion ProjectsColony
Success StoriesCampus TestimonialsRecolonization FAQsUndergraduatesGeneral Info & ResourcesAwardsAnnual Award WinnersAnnual Award Applications & DescriptionsUndergraduate Chapter AwardsIndividual AwardsGraduate Chapter AwardsCourageous Leader AwardCourageous Leader Award NominationsDistinguished Fiji AwardCOVID-19 Guidance 2020Join the Fight Against Hazing#JoinTheFight CampaignHazing Prevention PlanHazing Prevention ResourcesPledge to Join the FightGraduate RelationsPig DinnerGraduate Communication ServicesPhilanthropy & ServiceExamples of Philanthropy & ServicePhilanthropic PartnersImmortal Phi GamImmortal Phi Gam Sign-UpRecruitmentRecruitment ProgramsChapterBuilder ResourcesChapterBuilder Contact Update FormShop FijiOfficers & ChairmenChapter PaymentChapterBuilder ResourcesManualsReporting FormsChapter Progress ReportOfficers CalendarOrder Chapter SuppliesUpdate Chapter RosterEducationAcademicsHealth & Safety EducationAlcohol-Free HousingHealth & Safety Program RequestMental Health EducationSocial Strengths ProgramSocial Strengths E-ManualMember EducationNew Member EducationUIFIRisk ManagementLearning Portal (LMS)EventsArchives WeekendEkklesia172nd Ekklesia Registration172nd Ekklesia ResourcesFiji Academy2021 Academy Registration2021 Academy Vendor InfoAcademy ResourcesThe Leadership InstitutePig DinnerThe Summit SeriesEvents CalendarGraduatesNot For College Days AloneGraduate ChaptersGraduate Chapter DirectoryGraduate Chapter ResourcesUndergraduate Chapter DirectoryGraduate Dues ProgramPay Graduate DuesRecent GraduatesCareer ResourcesConnectEngageGiveSenior Celebration Week 2020Support the Educational FoundationUpdate Your Contact InformationGraduate Volunteers & AdvisorsVolunteer OpportunitiesSearch for OpportunitiesApply as a FacilitatorAdvisor ResourcesPL Monthly UpdateAwardsJoin the Fight Against HazingLearning Portal (LMS)HousingBest PracticesReserve StudyHouse Corporation Tools & ResourcesGraduate Communication ServicesCOVID-19 GuidanceDigital Repository ResourcesHouse Corporation NewsletterPreferred PartnersWebinars1848 Properties, Inc.EventsEkklesiaFiji AcademyPig DinnerEvents CalendarAdd an eventParents & FriendsAbout UsPhi Gamma Delta At-A-GlanceParents InfoRecruitmentFinancial CommitmentNo Hazing PolicyBuilding Courageous LeadersOrigin & PurposeThe Leadership InstituteJoining a FraternityVolunteer OpportunitiesShop FijiBenefits of Phi Gamma DeltaLifelong FriendshipEducationPledge EducationHazing PreventionHealth & Safety ProgrammingLeadership DevelopmentThe Leadership InstituteFiji AcademyTaking the LeadUndergraduate Interfraternity InstitutePhilanthropy & ServiceGraduate Advisor & Staff SupportGraduate AdvisorsField SecretariesScholarshipsAcademic Achievement AwardsChapter-Restricted ScholarshipsBlack Diamond AwardExpansionOverview & TimelineExpansion ProjectsColony Success StoriesCampus TestimonialsRecolonization FAQsContact UsContact FormChapter DirectoryStaff DirectorySubmit NewsNews & MediaThe Phi Gamma Delta MagazineCurrent IssuePast IssuesCirculation PolicyMagazine PreferencesSubmit NewsNewsAd Astra NotificationCurrent NewsThe Friday LetterAdministrative EditionGood News EditionBeginning of the Year RemindersSubmit NewsMediaGraphicsMedia ClipsStyle Guide & Graphic StandardsSongs of Phi Gamma DeltaGraduate Communication ServicesMailings & ProjectsMailing Request FormDiscount PackagesMailing PackageMailing Package AgreementPig Dinner PackagePig Dinner Package AgreementResources & VendorsFoundationGiving OptionsGive Now - USGive Now - CanadaGifts in Honor/MemoryMatching GiftsPlanned GivingThe ParliamentPersistence ClubDay of BrotherhoodEducational FoundationHistoryBoard of DirectorsContact UsFoundation of CanadaHistoryBoard of DirectorsGive Now - Foundation of CanadaScholarshipsScholarships & What We FundAcademic ScholarshipsHealth & Safety EducationThe Leadership InstituteChapter House Education Fund (CHEF)
Search:
Search
Privacy Policy of the Fraternity of Phi Gamma Delta and the Phi Gamma Delta Educational Foundation
Use of Links
Throughout our Web pages, we provide links to other servers which may contain information of interest to our readers. We take no responsibility for, and exercise no control over, the organizations, views, or accuracy of the information contained on other servers.Creating a text link from your Web site to our site does not require permission. If you have a link you'd like us to consider adding to our Web site, please send an email to phigam@phigam.org with the subject "Link request."
Use of Text and Images
If you would like to publish information that you find on our Web site, please send your request to phigam@phigam.org. Where text or images are posted on our site with the permission of the original copyright holder, a copyright statement appears at the bottom of the page.
Web Site Privacy Policy
We have created this statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. We do not collect personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. This policy is your guide to how we will handle information we learn about you from your visit to our Web site.
Reading or Downloading
We collect and store only the following information about you: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account, or cornell.edu if you are connecting from Cornell University's domain), the date and time you access our site, and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked to our site.
We use the information we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors.
Online Profile Updates and Donations
If you complete the Profile update form and share your personally identifying information, this information will be used only to provide you with more targeted content. We may use your contact information to send further information about our organization or to contact you when necessary. You may always opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the "Opt Out" section below.
Sending us an Email
You also may decide to send us personally identifying information, for example, in an electronic mail message containing a question or comment, or by filling out a Web form that provides us this information. We use personally identifying information from email primarily to respond to your requests. We may forward your email to other employees who are better able to answer you questions. We may also use your email to contact you in the future about our programs that may be of interest.
We want to be very clear: We will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. Except as might be required by law, we do not share any information we receive with any outside parties.
If you sign up for one of our email lists, we will only send you the kinds of information you have requested. We won't share your name or email address with any outside parties.
Opt-Out or Change Your Contact Information
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us through a special online form. You may choose to receive only specific communications or none at all. You may also update your contact information previously provided to us through another online form. You can not remove yourself from our database, but you can prevent unwanted communication.
Questions about our policies
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at: phigam@phigam.org
Find a Brother
Find a Chapter
Address Update
Manage a Chapter
New Member Registration
Donate to the Foundation
© 2016-2020 Phi Gamma Delta 1201 Red Mile Road, P.O. Box 4599 Lexington, Kentucky 40544-4599 859.255.1848    phigam@phigam.org
Facebook Twitter Instagram Linked In Youtube
Contact Us     Privacy Policy
